Guide to the Seattle Department of Parks and Recreation Planning, Construction and Maintenance Records 1928-1994
Seattle Municipal Archives
- Project files, 1928-1994
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Chronological File Jan. - Feb., 1971 (Box-folder 18/9)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Chronological File March, 1971 (Box-folder 18/10)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Chronological File May - June, 1971 (Box-folder 18/11)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Chronological File April, 1971 (Box-folder 18/12)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Chronological File July - August, 1971 (Box-folder 18/13)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Chronological File Sept. - October, 1971 (Box-folder 18/14)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Chronological File Nov. - Dec., 1971 (Box-folder 18/15)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Chronological File Jan. - May, 1972 (Box-folder 18/16)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Chronological File June - August, 1972 (Box-folder 18/17)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Chronological File Sept. - Dec., 1972 (Box-folder 18/18)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Correspondence, 1972 (Box-folder 18/19)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Correspondence Jan. - April, 1973 (Box-folder 18/20)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Correspondence, 1973 (Box-folder 18/21)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Memoranda, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 18/22)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Memoranda May - June, 1973 (Box-folder 19/1)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Memoranda June - August, 1973 (Box-folder 19/2)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Memoranda, 1973 (Box-folder 19/3)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Correspondence, 1974 (Box-folder 19/4)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Correspondence, 1975 (Box-folder 19/5)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Project File, 1969 (Box-folder 19/6)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Project File (includes maps drawings), 1970-1972 (Box-folder 19/7)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Project File, 1972 (Box-folder 19/8)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Project File Jan. - June, 1973 (Box-folder 19/9)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Project File July - December, 1973 (Box-folder 19/10)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Project File Jan. - April, 1974 (Box-folder 19/11)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Project File May, 1974 (Box-folder 19/12)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Project File June, 1974 (Box-folder 19/13)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Project File July, 1974 (Box-folder 19/14)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Project File Aug. - Sept., 1974 (Box-folder 19/15)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Project File Nov. - Dec., 1974 (Box-folder 19/16)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Project File Jan. - December, 1975 (Box-folder 19/17)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Project File Jan. - December, 1976 (Box-folder 19/18)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Project File, 1977 (Box-folder 19/19)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton Jan. - July, 1978 (Box-folder 19/20)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Project File July - Dec, 1978 (Box-folder 19/21)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Project File Jan. - June, 1979 (Box-folder 20/1)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Project File July - Dec, 1979 (Box-folder 20/2)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Project File, 1980 (Box-folder 20/3)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Project File, 1981 (Box-folder 20/4)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Project File, 1982 (Box-folder 20/5)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Project File, 1983 (Box-folder 20/6)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton General, 1984 (Box-folder 20/7)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton Contracts Boulevard Excavating - Removal of Buildings, 1973 (Box-folder 20/8)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton Contracts Center Dozing - Removal of Buildings, 1973 (Box-folder 20/9)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton - Contracts - Hyco Overhead Systems, 1973 (Box-folder 20/10)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton - Hyco, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 20/11)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Contracts - ICONCO, 1973 (Box-folder 20/12)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Contracts - ICONCO Removal of Buildings, 1973 (Box-folder 20/13)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Contracts Armstrong / Lehrer Forward Thrust, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 20/14)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton: Contracts #1 John Morse Assoc., 1972-1973 (Box-folder 20/15)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton Contract F. Mann Architect, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 20/16)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton Master Plan Contracts Dan Kiley Partners Contracts II, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 20/17)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton Consulting Engineers Contract No. 1, 1972 (Box-folder 20/18)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton Consulting Engineers J.J. Milligan Contract No. 11, 1973 (Box-folder 20/19)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton - Contracts Consulting Engineers J. J. Milligan Contract No. 111, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 20/20)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton - Contracts Consulting Engineers J.J. Milligan - Contract IV, 1973 (Box-folder 20/21)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton - Contracts Consulting Engineers J.J. Milligan Contract IV, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 20/22)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton Newspaper Clippings, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 20/23)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton Newspaper Clippings, 1974 (Box-folder 20/24)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton Newspaper Clippings, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 20/25)
  - Discovery Park / Fort Lawton Newspaper Clippings, 1979-1983 (Box-folder 20/26)
  - Dock Parks, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 20/27)
  - Dunlap Heights Playground, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 20/28)
  - Duwamish Waterway Park - Shoreline Development Permit, 1980 (Box-folder 20/29)
  - Duwamish Waterway Park, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 20/30)
  - Duwamish Waterway Park - Construction, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 20/31)
  - East Queen Anne Playground, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 20/32)
  - Eckstein Community Center, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 21/1)
  - Eckstein Community Center, 1978 (Box-folder 21/2)
  - Eckstein Community Center Site Selection Report Final Draft, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 21/3)
  - Eckstein Community Center Jan. - June, 1979 (Box-folder 21/4)
  - Eckstein Community Center July - Dec., 1979 (Box-folder 21/5)
  - Eckstein Community Center / Ravenna - Bryant Community Assoc., 1980 (Box-folder 21/6)
  - Eckstein Community Center / Ravenna - Bryant Community Assoc., 1981 (Box-folder 21/7)
  - Eckstein Community Center / Ravenna Elementary School Site, 1982 (Box-folder 21/8)
  - Evans Pool Rehabilitation Contract, 1972 (Box-folder 21/9)
  - Evans Pool Rehabilitation Project File Jan. - July, 1972 (Box-folder 21/10)
  - Evans Pool Rehabilitation Project File Aug. - Dec., 1972 (Box-folder 21/11)
  - Evans Pool Rehabilitation, 1973 (Box-folder 21/12)
  - Evans Pool Roof, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 21/13)
  - Evans Pool Spa, 1983 (Box-folder 21/14)
  - Evans Pool Newspaper Clippings, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 21/15)
  - Fauntleroy Park - Property Description Acquisition, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 21/16)
  - Fauntleroy Park, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 21/17)
  - Fiftieth Street Tennis Courts, 1975 (Box-folder 21/18)
  - Firehouse Park - Construction, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 21/19)
  - Firehouse Park, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 21/20)
  - First Hill Mini Park Correspondence, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 21/21)
  - First Hill Mini Park - Photographs (includes Prints Negatives of Ground Aerial Shots), 1968 (Box-folder 21/22)
  - First Hill Park - Financial / Finding, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 21/23)
  - First Hill Park - Findings - Application to US HUD Open Space Grant in Aid, 1968 (Box-folder 21/24)
  - First Hill Mini Park - Property Description Acquisition (includes maps drawings), 1968-1971 (Box-folder 21/25)
  - First Hill Mini Park - Planning, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 21/26)
  - First Hill Mini Park, 1973 (Box-folder 21/27)
  - First Hill Mini Park Construction, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 21/28)
  - First Hill Park - Design Consultant Contract Budget, 1977 (Box-folder 21/29)
  - First Hill Mini Park Construction, 1977 (Box-folder 21/30)
  - First Hill Mini Park Construction, 1978 (Box-folder 21/31)
  - First Hill Mini Park, 1979 (Box-folder 21/32)
  - First Hill Park, 1982 (Box-folder 21/33)
  - First Hill Mini Park - Newspaper Clippings, 1975 (Box-folder 21/34)
  - First and Seneca Park (includes CF 265005, photograph, and drawing), 1969-1972 (Box-folder 22/1)
  - Floodlighting Program, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 22/2)
  - Fort Dent / South Area Park - Contracts Agreements, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 22/3)
  - Fort Dent / South Area Park - Site Studies, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 22/4)
  - Fort Dent / South Area Park (includes photograph map), 1968-1972 (Box-folder 22/5)
  - Fort Dent / South Area Park Jan. - June, 1973 (Box-folder 22/6)
  - Fort Dent / South Park July - December, 1973 (Box-folder 22/7)
  - Fort Dent / South Park Jan. - June, 1974 (Box-folder 22/8)
  - Fort Dent / South Area Park July - Dec., 1974 (Box-folder 22/9)
  - Fort Dent / South Area Park (includes architectural drawings), 1975 (Box-folder 22/10)
  - Fort Dent / South Area Park, 1976 (Box-folder 22/11)
  - Fort Dent / South Area Park, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 22/12)
  - Fort Dent / South Area Park - Newspaper Clippings, 1969-1977 (Box-folder 22/13)
  - Foster Island Bridge Replacement, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 22/14)
  - Foster Island Bridge Replacement - Specifications, 1976 (Box-folder 22/15)
  - Freeway Park - Project Description, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 22/16)
  - Freeway Park - Acquisition, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 22/17)
  - Freeway Park - Funding, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 22/18)
  - Freeway Park - Financial, 1969-1975 (Box-folder 22/19)
  - Freeway Park - Tripartite Agreement, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 22/20)
  - Freeway Park - Contracts and Agreements, 1969-1975 (Box-folder 22/21)
  - Freeway Park - Design Services Contract, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 22/22)
  - Freeway Park - Environmental Impact Statement, 1974 (Box-folder 22/23)
  - Freeway Park - Normandie Apartments Site, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 22/24)
  - Freeway Park - Central Park Project Administration Services Contract for Construction, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 22/25)
  - Freeway Park - Model (includes photographs), 1974-1975 (Box-folder 23/1)
  - Freeway Park: Project File, 1969 (Box-folder 23/2)
  - Freeway Park: Project File, 1970 (Box-folder 23/3)
  - Freeway Park: Project File Jan. -May, 1971 (Box-folder 23/4)
  - Freeway Park - Project File June August, 1971 (Box-folder 23/5)
  - Freeway Park: Project File Sept. - Dec., 1971 (Box-folder 23/6)
  - Freeway Park: Project File Jan. - March, 1972 (Box-folder 23/7)
  - Freeway Park: Project File April - June, 1972 (Box-folder 23/8)
  - Freeway Park: Project File July - Dec., 1972 (Box-folder 23/9)
  - Freeway Park: Project File Jan. - May, 1973 (Box-folder 23/10)
  - Freeway Park: Project File June - Dec., 1973 (Box-folder 23/11)
  - Freeway Park: Jan - March, 1974 (Box-folder 23/12)
  - Freeway Park: April - July, 1974 (Box-folder 23/13)
  - Freeway Park: Project File Aug. - Dec., 1974 (Box-folder 23/14)
  - Freeway Park: Project File, 1975 (Box-folder 23/15)
  - Freeway Park - Project File, 1976 (Box-folder 23/16)
  - Freeway Park, 1977 (Box-folder 23/17)
  - Freeway Park: Environmental Impact Statement, 1974 (Box-folder 23/18)
  - Freeway Park: Fire Protection, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 23/19)
  - Freeway Park: Washington State Highway Commission, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 23/20)
  - Freeway Park - Washington State Highway Commission, 1975 (Box-folder 23/21)
  - Freeway Park: Tsutakawa Sculptural / Naramore Fountain, 1974 (Box-folder 23/22)
  - Freeway Park: American Legion Foundation, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 23/23)
  - Freeway Park - East Plaza Garage - Financial, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 24/1)
  - Freeway Park - East Plaza Garage: Schedule, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 24/2)
  - Freeway Park - East Plaza Garage: Contracts Agreements, 1971 (Box-folder 24/3)
  - Freeway Park - East Plaza Garage: Legal, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 24/4)
  - Freeway Park - East Plaza Garage: Project File, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 24/5)
  - Freeway Park - East Plaza Garage: Correspondence Project File, 1971 (Box-folder 24/6)
  - Freeway Park - East Plaza Garage Project File, 1972 (Box-folder 24/7)
  - Freeway Park - East Plaza Garage, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 24/8)
  - Freeway Park: East Plaza Parking Garage, 1974 (Box-folder 24/9)
  - Freeway Park: Safety and Fountain Improvements, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 24/10)
  - Freeway Park: Safety Fountain Improvements, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 24/11)
  - Freeway Park: Cost Allocations, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 24/12)
  - Freeway Park: Newspaper Clippings, 1970-1980 (Box-folder 24/13)
  - Freeway Park: Drawings, undated (Box-folder 24/14)
  - Freeway Park: Drawings, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 24/15)
  - Fremont Canal Park Shoreline Development Permit (includes photographs), 1979-1980 (Box-folder 24/16)
  - Fremont Canal Park: Budget, 1978-1983 (Box-folder 24/17)
  - Fremont Canal Park: Army Corps of Engineers, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 24/18)
  - Fremont Canal Park: Artwork (includes color slides photography), 1979-1981 (Box-folder 24/19)
  - Fremont Canal Park Construction (Incl. Drawings), 1979-1981 (Box-folder 24/20)
  - Fremont Canal Park Dedication, 1981 (Box-folder 24/21)
  - Fremont Canal Park Project File, 1978 (Box-folder 24/22)
  - Fremont Canal Park Project File, 1979 (Box-folder 24/23)
  - Fremont Canal Park Project File, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 24/24)
  - Fremont Canal Park Newspaper Clippings, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 24/25)
  - Fremont Mini Park, 1974 (Box-folder 24/26)
  - Frink Park Improvements, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 24/27)
  - Frink and Colman Park Bridges, 1979-1984 (Box-folder 24/28)
  - Garfield Community Center - Medgar Evers Swimming Pool, 1968 (Box-folder 25/1)
  - Garfield Community Center - Medgar Evers Swimming Pool, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 25/2)
  - Garfield Community Center - Medgar Evers Pool Dedication, 1970 (Box-folder 25/3)
  - Garfield Community Center - Medgar Evers Swimming Pool Contracts, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 25/4)
  - Garfield Community Center - Medgar Evers Pool (includes drawings of reader board), 1975-1976 (Box-folder 25/5)
  - Garfield Community Center - Medgar Evers Pool Repairs, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 25/6)
  - Garfield Playfield Improvements, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 25/7)
  - Garfield Playfield Expansion, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 25/8)
  - Garfield Playfield Improvements - "Wall of Respect" Art Work, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 25/9)
  - Garfield Community Center Newspaper Clippings, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 25/10)
  - Garfield Running Track Playfield / Powell Barnett Park, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 25/11)
  - Genesee Park Acquisition, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 25/12)
  - Genesee Park, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 25/13)
  - Genesee Park - Contracts, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 25/14)
  - Genesee Park Soil Investigation, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 25/15)
  - Genesee Park Soil Surcharge Test Results, 1970-1978 (Box-folder 25/16)
  - Genesee Park, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 25/17)
  - Genesee Park, 1976 (Box-folder 25/18)
  - Genesee Park, 1977 (Box-folder 25/19)
  - Genesee Park Phase II Street Vacation 42nd Ave. S., 1975-1977 (Box-folder 25/20)
  - Genesee Park Phase II, 1978 (Box-folder 25/21)
  - Genesee Park Playfield Phase II Contracts, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 25/22)
  - Genesee Park Phase II, 1978 (Box-folder 25/23)
  - Genesee Park Phase II, 1979 (Box-folder 25/24)
  - Genesee Park Phase II, 1980-1984 (Box-folder 25/25)
  - Genesee Park Newspaper Clippings, undated (Box-folder 25/26)
  - Georgetown Playfield Rehab Plans, 1977 (Box-folder 25/27)
  - Georgetown Playfield, 1965-1970 (Box-folder 25/28)
  - Georgetown Playfield, 1976 (Box-folder 25/29)
  - Georgetown Playfield, 1977 (Box-folder 25/30)
  - Georgetown Playfield, 1978 (Box-folder 25/31)
  - Georgetown Playfield, 1979 (Box-folder 25/32)
  - Georgetown Playfield, 1980-1985 (Box-folder 25/33)
  - Georgetown Playfield Drawings Maps, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 25/34)
  - Georgetown Playfield Contract Specifications, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 25/35)
  - Golden Gardens Park Sewer, 1969-1975 (Box-folder 26/1)
  - Golden Gardens Park Acquisition, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 26/2)
  - Golden Gardens Park, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 26/3)
  - Golden Gardens Park Design Services Contract, Drawing, and Agreements, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 26/4)
  - Golden Gardens Park, 1975 (Box-folder 26/5)
  - Golden Gardens Park Project File, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 26/6)
  - Golden Gardens Park, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 26/7)
  - Golden Gardens Park Slide, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 26/8)
  - Golden Gardens Park Slide, 1974 (Box-folder 26/9)
  - Golden Gardens Park Slide, 1975 (Box-folder 26/10)
  - Golden Gardens Park - Slide - Engineering Drawings Photography, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 26/11)
  - Golden Gardens Park - Slide (includes photographs), 1976-1984 (Box-folder 26/12)
  - Golden Gardens Park Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 26/13)
  - Graphics Sign Study Contracts, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 26/14)
  - Graphics Sign Study Project File, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 26/15)
  - Graphics Sign Study Project File, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 26/16)
  - Green Lake Boating Sailing Facility Project History, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 26/17)
  - Green Lake Boating Sailing Facility Design Contract, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 26/18)
  - Green Lake Boating Sailing Facility Project File, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 26/19)
  - Green Lake Boating Sailing Facilities Project File, 1975 (Box-folder 26/20)
  - Green Lake Boating Sailing Facility Project File, 1976 (Box-folder 26/21)
  - Green Lake Boating Sailing Facility, 1977 (Box-folder 26/22)
  - Green Lake Boating Sailing Facility Project File, 1978 (Box-folder 26/23)
  - Green Lake Boating Sailing Facilities Project File, 1979 (Box-folder 26/24)
  - Green Lake Boating and Sailing Facility / Small Craft Center Project File, 1980 (Box-folder 26/25)
  - Green Lake Boating Sailing Facility / Small Craft Center Project File ( includes dedication ), 1980-1981 (Box-folder 26/26)
  - Green Lake Boating Sailing Facility / Small Craft Center - Newspaper Clippings, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 26/27)
  - Green Lake Boat Rental Facility, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 26/28)
  - Green Lake Bike Path, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 26/29)
  - Green Lake Community Center Improvements - Contracts, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 26/30)
  - Green Lake Community Center Improvements, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 26/31)
  - Green Lake Community Center Improvements, 1975 (Box-folder 26/32)
  - Green Lake Community Center Improvements, 1976 (Box-folder 26/33)
  - Green Lake Utilization Study, 1967 (Box-folder 27/1)
  - " History of Green Lake Park " Don Sherwood, 1978 (Box-folder 27/2)
  - Green Lake Park Children's Play Area, 1968 (Box-folder 27/3)
  - Green Lake Master Plan, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 27/4)
  - Green Lake - Bathhouse Theatre, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 27/5)
  - Green Lake Shorewall, 1975 (Box-folder 27/6)
  - Green Lake / Lower Woodland Food Concessions, 1979 (Box-folder 27/7)
  - Green Lake Community Center Paving Improvements, 1984 (Box-folder 27/8)
  - Green Lake Stretching Station, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 27/9)
  - Green Lake Stretching Station Photographs ( Polaroid ), 1982 (Box-folder 27/10)
  - Green Lake Park Improvements Phase II, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 27/11)
  - Green Lake Park Phase II Improvements, 1978 (Box-folder 27/12)
  - Green Lake Park Phase II Improvements, 1978 (Box-folder 27/13)
  - Green Lake Park Phase II Improvements, 1978 (Box-folder 27/14)
  - Green Lake Park Phase II Improvements, 1979 (Box-folder 27/15)
  - Green Lake Park Phase II Improvements, 1979 (Box-folder 27/16)
  - Green Lake Park Phase II Improvements - Construction Meeting Reports May - July, 1979 (Box-folder 27/17)
  - Green Lake Park Phase II Improvements - Construction Meeting Reports Aug. - Dec., 1979 (Box-folder 27/18)
  - Green Lake Park Phase II Improvements ( includes preliminary master plan ), 1980 (Box-folder 27/19)
  - Green Lake Park Phase II Improvements - Construction Meeting Reports, 1980 (Box-folder 27/20)
  - Green Lake Park Phase II Improvements - Construction, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 27/21)
  - Green Lake Park Phase II Improvements Design Services Contract, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 27/22)
  - Green Lake Park Phase II Improvements, 1982 (Box-folder 27/23)
  - Green Lake Park Phase III Improvements, 1983 (Box-folder 27/24)
  - Green Lake Park Phase III Improvements, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 27/25)
  - Green Lake Park Phase III Improvements - Budget, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 27/26)
  - Green Lake Park Phase III Improvements - Design Services Contract, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 27/27)
  - Green Lake Park Newspaper Clippings, 1972-1980 (Box-folder 27/28)
  - Green Lake Use Requests, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 27/29)
  - Greenbelts, 1959-1971 (Box-folder 28/1)
  - Greenbelts - Acquisition, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 28/2)
  - Greenbelts Correspondence, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 28/3)
  - Greenbelts - Planning, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 28/4)
  - Greenbelts - Financial, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 28/5)
  - Greenbelts - West Duwamish, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 28/6)
  - Greenbelts - Parkway, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 28/7)
  - Greenbelts - Highland ( includes photographs ), 1969-1973 (Box-folder 28/8)
  - Greenbelts - Harrison Ridge, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 28/9)
  - Hamlin Park Correspondence, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 28/10)
  - Hamlin Park, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 28/11)
  - Hamlin Park Maps Drawings, 1970 (Box-folder 28/12)
  - Harborview View Park, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 28/13)
  - Harrison Mini - Park, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 28/14)
  - Helene Madison Pool, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 28/15)
  - Helene Madison / Ingraham Swimming Pool, 1968-1975 (Box-folder 28/16)
  - Helene Madison / Ingraham Swimming Pool Newspaper Clippings, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 28/17)
  - Hiawatha Ballfield Lighting, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 28/18)
  - Hiawatha Playfield Improvements ( includes drawings ), 1980-1981 (Box-folder 28/19)
  - Hiawatha Playfield Play Area, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 28/20)
  - Highland Park Shelterhouse Rehabilitation, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 28/21)
  - High Point Community Center, 1978 (Box-folder 28/22)
  - High Point Community Center Contract Budget, 1979-1983 (Box-folder 28/23)
  - High Point Community Center, 1979 (Box-folder 28/24)
  - High Point Community Center, 1980 (Box-folder 28/25)
  - High Point Community Center, 1981 (Box-folder 28/26)
  - High Point Community Center, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 28/27)
  - High Point Community Center Art Window, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 28/28)
  - High Point / Central West Seattle Playfield Contract Budget, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 29/1)
  - High Point / Central West Seattle Playfield, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 29/2)
  - High Point / Central West Seattle Playfield, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 29/3)
  - High Point / Central West Seattle Playfield - Drawings, 1979 (Box-folder 29/4)
  - Hing Hay Park Newspaper Clippings, undated (Box-folder 29/5)
  - Hing Hay Park, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 29/6)
  - Hing Hay Park, 1972 (Box-folder 29/7)
  - Hing Hay Park, 1973 (Box-folder 29/8)
  - Hing Hay Park, 1974 (Box-folder 29/9)
  - Hing Hay Park, 1975 (Box-folder 29/10)
  - Hing Hay Park, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 29/11)
  - Horton Hill Park, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 29/12)
  - Horton Hill Park, 1977 (Box-folder 29/13)
  - Horton Hill Park, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 29/14)
  - Hutchinson Playground, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 29/15)
  - Hunter Boulevard, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 29/16)
  - Hunter Boulevard Community Correspondence, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 29/17)
  - Hutchinson Shelter, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 29/18)
  - Hutchinson Shelterhouse / Community Center, 1976-1980 (Box-folder 29/19)
  - Interbay, 1977-1981 (Box-folder 29/20)
  - International District Mini Park, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 29/21)
  - International District Children's Park (Incl. Photographs), 1979-1983 (Box-folder 29/22)
  - International District Children's Park / Mini Park (Incl. Drawings), 1979-1980 (Box-folder 29/23)
  - International District Mini Park, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 29/24)
  - International District Mini Park / Children's Park, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 29/25)
  - International District Mini Park / Children's Park Newspaper Clippings, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 29/26)